starzplay.pk 2018-06-12

# STARZ PLAY | Watch Featured Movies and Original Series

**STARZ PLAY - PRIVACY POLICY**

At Playco Entertainment FZ LLC, which shall include our affiliates and subsidiaries (" **Playco** ", " **we** ", " **our** " or " **us** ") your privacy is very important to us and we are committed to protecting and respecting it.

This policy (together with our Terms of Use) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.

By visiting  **www.starzplay.com  **(the " **Site** ") you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.

 **INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU**

We may collect and process the following data about you:

  * **Information you give us.**  You may give us information about you by filling in forms on our Site or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. This includes information you provide when you register to use our Site, subscribe to our Service, (if applicable) participate in discussion boards or other social media functions on or related to our Site, enter a Competition, promotion or survey and when you report a problem with our Site. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, financial and credit card information, and/or personal description.
  * **Information we collect about you.**  With regard to each of your visits to our Site we may automatically collect the following information or statistical data:
    * technical information, including the internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer/device to the internet which identifies your computer/device, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of our demographic and profile data known as traffic data so that data, such as webpages, can be sent to you; and
    * information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our Site (including date and time); page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), methods used to browse away from the page, and any phone number used to call our customer service number.
  * **Information we receive from other sources.**  We may receive information about you if you use any of the other websites we operate or the other services we provide. We are also working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, advertising networks, analytics providers and search information providers) and may receive information about you from them.

 **COOKIES**

We use cookies to distinguish you from other users of our Site. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our Site and also allows us to improve our Site. A cookie is a very small text document, which often contains an anonymous unique identifier.

Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our Site, and as such you are able to set your browser to decline cookies and/or delete them. If you do so, you will still be able to access our Site, but you may find that some areas or pages do not function as smoothly as they might with cookies enabled.

We will use the following cookies:

  * **Strictly necessary cookies.** These are cookies that are required for the operation of our Site. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our Site;
  * **Analytical/performance cookies**. They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our Site when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our Site works;
  * **Functionality cookies**. These are used to recognise you when you return to our Site; and
  * **Targeting cookies**. These cookies record your visit to our Site, the pages you have visited, the Content Pages and Content you have viewed, and the links you have followed. We will use this information to make our Site and the advertising displayed on it more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties for this purpose.

 **USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION**

We use information held about you in the following ways:

  * **Information you give to us.**  We will use this information:
    * to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information that you request from us;
    * with your consent, to provide you, or permit selected third parties to provide you, with information about goods or services we feel may interest you. If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please contact us at [ **support@starzplayarabia.com**](mailto:support@starzplayarabia.com)
    * to notify you about changes to our Service(s); and
    * to ensure that content from our Site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer or other device.

  * **Information we collect about you.**  We will use this information:
    * to administer our Site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
    * to improve our Site to ensure that Content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer or other device;
    * to allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service, when you choose to do so;
    * as part of our efforts to keep our Site safe and secure; and
    * to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you.

  * **Information we receive from other sources.  ** We may combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We may use this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive).

 **DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We may share your personal information with any member of our corporate group.

We may share your information with selected third parties including:

  * business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you;
  * advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others; and/or
  * analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our Site.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;
  * if Playco or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets; and/or
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and/or other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Playco, our customers, or others.

 **STORAGE AND SECURITY**

Our Site is secured and encrypted for your privacy. However, the data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the Middle East. It may also be processed by staff operating outside the Middle East who work for us or for one of our suppliers. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

 **THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

Our Site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of third parties, our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. Links to or from external websites not owned or controlled by us do not constitute an endorsement by us of the products or information presented therein.

If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

 **CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.

 **CONTACT US**

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [**support@starzplayarabia.com**](mailto:support@starzplayarabia.com)

 **REVISED 3 SEPTEMBER 2015 AND EFFECTIVE AS OF THE DATE POSTED**
